New York Coalition for Alternatives to Pesticides; Records apap151
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement, 1980-1999; 3; 4.50 cubic ft.
  - Brodsky Pesticide Sunset Bill A.9107, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 12)
  - Buffalo -- Pest Management Board, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 13)
  - Buffalo Pest Management Board, Pesticide Sunset Ordinance, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 14)
  - Canada -- United States Trade Agreement [CUSTA], Technical Working Group on Pesticides, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 15)
  - Central New York Environment, "Rebutting Arguments Against Pesticide Notification", 2001 February-2001 March (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 16)
  - City of Albany -- Department of Water and Water Supply, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 17)
  - Communities in Action -- Pesticide Ordinance In Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence from New Zealand on Reducing Herbicide Use and Government Pesticide Policy, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 19)
  - Environmental Associates of New York/NYPIRG, Excerpts from Pesticide Phase-out Manual, updated, Undated (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 20)
  - Environmental Impact Statement -- [Binder Contents] on risks due to use of Scourge, Dibrom14 and Malathion, 1979-1990 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 21-22)
  - Environmental Management Councils and Conservation Commissions, Background Information and NYCAP Appeal, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 23)
  - Federal Insecticide, Fungicide and Rodenticide Act [FIFRA] / NCAMP, 1987-1992 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 24)
  - Homeowner's Insurance / Pesticide Contamination, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 25)
  - Interim Report: The NYS Assembly Committee on Environmental Conservation's Oversight Investigation and Performance Audit of the NYSDEC, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 26-27)
  - "Into the Sunset", Photos, [1998?] (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 28)
  - Legal Actions Concerning Pesticide Use -- National, 1995-2002 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 29)
  - Legal Decisions in Cases Relating to Pesticides -- New York, 1989-1999 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 30)
  - Local Government Rights to Regulate Pesticides -- U.S. Supreme Court Case, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 31)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Buffalo, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 32)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Buffalo -- Pest Management Board, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 33)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Canada, 1993-2001 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 34)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Florida, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 35)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Long Island, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 36)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- New Jersey, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 37)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Orchard Park, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 38)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Rochester, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 39)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Rockland County, 1992-1995 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 40)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Rockland County, Sensible Pest Management Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 41)
  - Local Pest Management Laws -- Thurston County, Washington, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 42)
  - Maine State Legislature, Office of Policy and Legal Analysis, Final Report of the Commission to Study the Use of Herbicides, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 43)
  - Massachusetts -- Proposed Legislation Banning Use of Nonagricultural Pesticides, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 44)
  - NCAMP, Compilation of State and Local Pesticide Regulations with Related Articles, 1982-1995 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 45)
  - NYCAMP Testimony [Jay Feldman] on the Public's Exposure to pesticides Before U.S. House and Senate, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 46)
  - Neighbor Notification Law-Dept. of Environmental Conservation Guidelines, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 47)
  - Neighbor Notification -- NYCAP Information Packet Updates, and Memos, 1996-1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 48)
  - Neighbor Notification -- Pamela Hadad Hurst Testimony, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 49)
  - New Jersey -- State Executive Order on Use of IPM for Pest Management, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 50)
  - New York Healthy Schools Network, Bills in NYS Legislature [Memos in Support of], 1998 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 51)
  - New York State Attorney General / Environmental Protection Bureau, Correspondence and Notes, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 52)
  - New York State Attorney General, Legal Actions Concerning Pesticide Use, 1989; 2000-2002 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 53)
  - New York State Attorney General, Pest Control in Public Housing, Schools, and Parks: Urban Children at Risk, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 54)
  - New York State Attorney General, Pesticide Issues, 1999-2001 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 55)
  - New York State DEC, Pesticide Regulations, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 56)
  - New York State DEC, Rules and Regulations Relating to the Application of Pesticides -- Draft, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 57)
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets, Sound Agriculture Practices / Right to Farm -- Lawsuits, 1996-1999 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 58)
  - New York State Dept. of Environmental Conservation, Annual Report on New York State Pesticides Sales and Application, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 59)
  - New York State Dept. of Environmental Conservation, Integrated Pest Management Plan, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 60)
  - New York State Dept. of Environmental Conservation, Part 325 -- Rules and Regulation Relating to the Application of Pesticides, 2000 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 61)
  - New York State, Dept. of Environmental Conservation, Part 375 Hazardous Waste Disposal Site Remedial Program, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 62)
  - New York State, Dept. of Environmental Conservation, Proposed Antidegradation Review Process for New York State, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 63)
  - New York State, Dept. of Health, "Pesticide Poisoning Registry Report, 1995 and 1996", 1997 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 64)
  - New York State Education Dept., Neighbor Notification for Schools, 2001 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 65)
  - New York State, Environmental Conservation Law Relating to Pesticides, Circular 863, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 66)
  - New York State, Executive Chamber, IPM Program Implementation, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 67)
  - New York State Office of General Services, IPM Policies and Procedures, 1993-1995 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 1)
  - New York State Office of General Services, Pest Control through Integrated Pest Management, Position Paper, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 2)
  - New York State, Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law -- Summary, Guide, Articles, Correspondence, Sample Notices, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 3)
  - NYPIRG, Neighbor Notification, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 4)
  - NYPIRG, Sunset Ordinance Fact sheet and Action Alert, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 5)
  - Pest Management Board, Buffalo, Meeting Minutes and Related Articles, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 6)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Comparison of Sunset Ordinances in Buffalo and Albany County, 1995-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 7)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Meeting Minutes, Pest Management Plan, Phase-out Variance Reavest, 1998-2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 8)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Memoranda, Variance Requests, Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 9)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Pest Control Practices and Contracts, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 10)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Pest Control Practices and Contracts, Memos, Correspondence, and Minutes, 1998-2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 11)
  - Pest Management Committee [Albany County] -- Pesticide use, 1998-2003 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 12)
  - "Pest Management Practices: A Survey of Public School Districts in New York State, "NYS IPM Program, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 13)
  - Pesticide Action League, recent Changes in Pesticide Use in Southern Ontario and Canada, ca. 1992 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 14)
  - Pesticide Management Advisory Council [PMAC] Meeting- 2/9/00 and 12/20/00, Notes, Agendas, and NYS Documents (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 15)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification, history and Previous Legislation, 1995-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 16)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Albany County, 2000-2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 17)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Examples of School Notices, 2001-2002 19. Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law in New York State, Information Packet, 1999-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 18)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Nassau and Westchester Counties, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 20)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law -- NYCAP Letters of Support, 2001-2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 21)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Onondaga County, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 22)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Rensselear County, 2000-2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 23)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification Law, Various New York Counties, 2000-2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 24)
  - Pesticide Neighbor Notification, Pamela Hadad Hurst Testimony to Albany County Legislature in Support, 2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 25)
  - Pesticide Phase-out Proposals or Resolutions from Various New York State Communities, 1999-2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 26)
  - Pesticide Phase-out Proposals or Resolutions Outside of New York State, 1995-2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 27)
  - Pesticide Reduction Working Group / Pesticide Right-to-Know and Reduction Project, Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 28)
  - Pesticide Reporting Bill, Correspondence and Other Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 29)
  - Pesticide Reporting Law, Article, 1996-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 30)
  - Pesticide Use -- Jones Beach State Park Case, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 31)
  - Pesticide Use Reduction in Indonesia, 1988-1993 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 32)
  - Pesticide Use Reduction -- Unites States, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 33)
  - Phase-out / Sunset Ordinance Overview, New York State, ca. 2000 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 34)
  - "Poisoning the Public For Profit: Pesticide Use and Abuse in the Empire State", Report to New York State Assemble, 1990 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 35)
  - "Pro-Pesticides" Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 36)
  - Public Policy Dispute Resolution Forums, 1991-1996 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 37)
  - Rensselaer County Environmental Management Council / Pesticide Notification Law Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 38)
  - San Francisco Environment Code, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 39)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Arizona, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 40)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- California, 1988-1999 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 41)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Florida, 1989; 1994 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 42)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Hawaii, 1985-1988 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 43)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Louisiana, ca. 1985 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 44)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Maine, 1984-1998 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 45)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Massachusetts, 1988-1993 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 46)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Minnesota, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 47)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Mississippi, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 48)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- New Hampshire, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 49)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- New Jersey, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 50)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- New York, 1996-1998; Undated (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 51)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- North Carolina, 1987-1999 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 52)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Oregon, 1978-1991; Undated (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 53)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Pennsylvania, 1987-1993 (Box 2 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 54)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Rhode Island, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 1)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Texas, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 2)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Vermont, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 3)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Virginia, ca. 1980 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 4)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Washington, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 5)
  - Structural Pesticide Notification -- Proposed regulations by New York State DEC, 1997-1998 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 6)
  - Sunset Ordinance Information Packet, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 7)
  - Understanding Relevant Laws and Regulations, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 8)
  - United States, EPA, Office of Pesticide Programs, Ecological Effects Branch, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 9)
  - Westchester County -- Pest Management Committee, 1995-1997 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 10)
  - Women's Health and Dioxins from Tampons and Feminine Napkins [Federal Bill; HR-2900], 1998 (Box 3 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 11)
  - Bethlehem Pesticide Watch -- Talk by James Moore, Correspondence and Reports, 1998 (Box 4 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 1)
  - State Pesticide Use Laws -- Connecticut, 1988 (Box 4 (3-Pesticide Laws, Policy and Enforcement), Folder 2)
- Conferences, Classes and Workshops, 1985-2002; 4; 4.75 cubic ft.
  This series deals with the conferences that NYCAP planned, presented, participated in, or attended. Additionally, this series also includes some college classes on agriculture that were taught in cooperation with Tracy Frisch before the formation of NYCAP. There are also workshops included in this series, consisting of short classes or training sponsored by NYCAP. These files include conference planning meetings, correspondence with speakers and participants, attendance lists, advertisements, programs, schedules, location information, and speaker notes.
  - Another Way to Be Green: Learning with Gold Course Innovations, Meeting Agendas and Flyers, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 1)
  - Audubon Meetings re: West Nile Virus, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 2)
  - Avian Pesticides Meeting, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 3)
  - Bethlehem Pesticide Watch -- Talk notes, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 4)
  - Beyond Pesticides Forum -- Stop the Poisoning, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 5)
  - Binghamton -- area Conference on IPM for Schools, Municipalities, State Agencies, Hospitals, etc., 1995 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Landscape Gardeners' Association Conference '98 -- Remarks, Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 7)
  - Building the Sustainable Economy Conference, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 8)
  - Children and Pesticides -- Presentation Materials, 1995-2002 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 9)
  - Community and Public Service Program Agency Fair, University at Albany [SUNY], 1999 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 10)
  - Conference Flyers and Other Brief Descriptions, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 11)
  - Conference Materials -- Various Conferences, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 12)
  - Conference on IPM for Buildings and Grounds, Syracuse-area, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 13)
  - Conference Planning, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 14)
  - Conference Planning -- New York State Nurses Association / IPM, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 15)
  - Consumer's Union Pesticide Conference, Austin, Texas, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 16)
  - CSEA [Civil Service Employees Union] Statewide Conference on Occupational Safety and Health, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 17)
  - Earth Day Lobby Day, 2000 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 18)
  - Earth Day, Lobby Day, and Rally, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 19)
  - Effective Pest Control Conference, Hamilton/Fulton/Montgomery County BOCES, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 20)
  - Environmental Advocates -- Environment '97, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 21)
  - Environmental Roundtable with Eliot Spitzer and Hillary Clinton / Earth Day Lobby Day, 2001 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 22)
  - Facilities and Services Conference / Green Campus Green Community, SUNY -- Stony Brook, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 23)
  - GMO[Genetically Modifies Organisms] Lobby Day, 2002 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 24)
  - Health Effects of Pesticides on the Job Speech, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 25)
  - Herbicides and Right-of-Way Management -- Conference Binder, Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 26)
  - Hurst, Pam Hadad -- Speech to N.Y.S. Superintendents of Buildings and Grounds Association, Nassau County Chapter, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 27)
  - Integrated Pest Management for Healthcare Facilities Conference, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 28)
  - Integrated Pest Management for Nassau County Building and Grounds Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 29)
  - Integrated Pest Management for School Buildings and Grounds Conference, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 30)
  - Integrated Pest Management Teleconference, Reference Materials, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 31)
  - integrated Turf Management for Schools Conference, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 32)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Conference / Roadside Right of Way Information Packet, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 33)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 34)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, California's for Alternative to Toxics Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 35)
  - integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference -- Caltrans Involvement, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 36)
  - Integrated vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Conference Evaluations, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 37)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Correspondence and Contacts, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 38)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Co-sponsors-Planning and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 39)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Educational Display Materials, 1992-1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 40)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Educational Display List and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 41)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, Invites / Outreach, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 42)
  - Integrated Vegetation Management for Roadsides Training Conference, IPM Parishioners Association Information, 1995-1998 (Box 1 (4-Conferences, Classes and Workshops), Folder 43)